Justin Stutler <u>StutlerJustin@gmail.com</u> https://github.com/JustinStutler JStutler@usf.edu Tampa, Fl https://justinstutler.github.io/

Objective

Motivated Full Stack Web Developer and with the ability to develop web applications using JavaScript, HMTL, CSS, and SQL. Data Scientist with the ability to conduct analysis of data in python or R. Strong understanding of agile work environments and experience in leading teams.

Skills

Front-End: Javascript, HTML, CSS, React.js, Bootstrap

Back-End: SQL, Python, Go Data Science: Python, R

Project Management: Agile, Kanban, JIRA, Confluence, Git

Experience

MagMutual Insurance - Intern/ Contractor

May 2020 - December 2020

I quickly acquired proficiency in Javascript, HTML, CSS, and SQL, transitioning from a beginner to a competent developer within a few months. I successfully developed and deployed dynamic web applications, demonstrating my perseverance and learning capability. I adapted to the many standard project management tools such as Git, Agile, Kanban, JIRA, and Confluence.

PieHole - Baker/ Manager

2016-2018

Beginning as a baker, I learned many skills such as communication, problem-solving, time management, how to work well under pressure, and teamwork. Eventually, I became a manager and learned how to teach and lead others. Thanksgiving was particularly challenging with the large amount of orders, but this gave me the opportunity to lead a small team of 4 through the holidays.

Education

University of South Florida

Bachelor of Information Science - Enrolled (Web Development) (2022-2024, 3.58 GPA)

Kennesaw State University

Dean's List | Bachelor of Computer Science - Incomplete (2019-2021, 3.75 GPA)

University of North Georgia

Bachelor of Computer Science - Incomplete (2018-2019)

Milton High School

Computer Science Focus (Graduated Class of 2018, 3.89 GPA)

Extra Curricular

Player for Student-Run Overwatch Team at KSU (2019-2021)

Member of USF Brazilian Jiu-jitsu (2023-2024)

Member of USF Board Game Club (2022-2024)